<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An exploration of patient infomation of COVID in South Korea</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/an-exploration-of-patient-infomation-of-covid-in-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/an-exploration-of-patient-infomation-of-covid-in-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>require(tidyverse)My research topicCOVID-19 has rapidly become a worldwide pandemic since December in 2019, with the symtoms of fever, cough, fatigue, and clinic manifestation of maniground-glass lung changes, hypoxaemia, and deranged gastrointestinal, liver and renal function(???). For severe cases, the disease will deteriorate to severe fibrotic lung (which is called “Withe Lung” by Chinese doctors), and multi-organ failure (???).
Moreover, the virus has a high reproductive number (R0).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I am Green Ear Rabbit (Because I have a rabbit and it like vegetables, I also like vegetables, vegetable is green). I am an undergraduate student, and I am interested in epidemiology, clinical practice and statistical modeling.
It&amp;rsquo;s really interesting and exciting to learn how to make a blog in school. If there is any problems or conflicts, feel free to contact me via: greenearrabbit@163.com
I am also planning for my graduate school or research, if you wish coperation or willing to provide an opportunity, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jilin-hospitals-for-patients-with-fever</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/jilin-hospitals-for-patients-with-fever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/jilin-hospitals-for-patients-with-fever/</guid>
      <description>require(tidyverse) ## Loading required package: tidyverse## Warning: package &amp;#39;tidyverse&amp;#39; was built under R version 3.6.2## -- Attaching packages --------## v ggplot2 3.3.0 v purrr 0.3.4## v tibble 3.0.1 v dplyr 0.8.5## v tidyr 1.0.3 v stringr 1.4.0## v readr 1.3.1 v forcats 0.4.0## Warning: package &amp;#39;ggplot2&amp;#39; was built under R version 3.6.3## Warning: package &amp;#39;tibble&amp;#39; was built under R version 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My clinical notes 1: a patients with lupus erythematosus</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/my-clinical-notes-1-a-patients-with-lupus-erythematosus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/my-clinical-notes-1-a-patients-with-lupus-erythematosus/</guid>
      <description>A 19-year-old, rural, skinny girl diagnosed with lupus erythematosus.
Sometimes I met and talk with her in the ward. Some of our talking are very impressive to me, both reflect environmental and socail issues.
After I take notes on her symptoms, I still want to ask more things, even if I am not supposed to do. I am always interested in how does people get disease. The lupus erythematosus, why does this disease come to her, rather than those bad people who are expected to get disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My clinical notes 2: many people only know ther syphilis when blood donation</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/my-clinical-notes-2-many-people-only-know-ther-syphilis-when-blood-donation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/my-clinical-notes-2-many-people-only-know-ther-syphilis-when-blood-donation/</guid>
      <description>I feel so bored one afternon and I go to outpatient department, where I can talk and ask questions to the doctors when they are free.
“Many people got syphilis and are not be aware of that, but it’s not a problem. Because nowadays, people take antibotics often, you know, even for a cold. Tp. is so easy to be killed. Many patients found they were infected until they go to blood donation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My clinical notes 3: A schizophrenia patient</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/my-clinical-notes-3-a-schizophrenia-patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/my-clinical-notes-3-a-schizophrenia-patient/</guid>
      <description>One good weather day afternoon I sit in the public office and read a doctor’s book sleeply.
There is a new patient just accepted by the department. It’s a patient with schizophrenia, with liver cirrhosis, and were sent to hospital by apsychia.
Considering schizophrenia, he was put in a seperate and isolated ward.
I am just a student, and what I can do is only to go to ask patient’s history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R-visualization-of-epidemic-in-United-States</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/r-visualization-of-epidemic-in-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/r-visualization-of-epidemic-in-united-states/</guid>
      <description>My research topicCOVID-19 has rapidly become a worldwide pandemic since December in 2019. China has controled the domestic cases effectively and timely by a series of polcy, e.g lockdown of Wuhan city, close of schools and company. However, United States has become the epicenter of this outbreak.
U.S has adopted “mass screening” policy to identify cases, which is use rapid and wide testing to identify both active and inactive cases to control the further transmission.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>