<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/categories/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/categories/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical notes: Health Disparities</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/clinical-notes-health-disparities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/clinical-notes-health-disparities/</guid>
      <description>People in low-socioeconomic status are at a high risk of diseases and death. I saw two patients both diagnosed with intracranial tuberculoma. One of them was a middle-aged and high-income man. He lived in a VIP ward for three months. He even wanted to live in the ward for several more days, after the doctors said that he is fully recovered. The other one is a 19-year-old rural boy, he came to city alone for a higher salary work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How does pescetarian diet affect health: An breif human experiment</title>
      <link>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/how-does-pescetarian-diet-affect-health-an-breif-human-experiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://green-ear-rabbit.github.io/blog/1/01/01/how-does-pescetarian-diet-affect-health-an-breif-human-experiment/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionTo evaluate the effect the health effect of pescetarian diet, an two-month’s intervention study was conducted on a 19-year-old female, from April, 6th to Jun 12th, in 2019. Food frequency questionnaire were answered by the participant at baseline. Blood glucose, hemoglobin A1c (HbA1c), blood urea nitrogen (BUN), high-density lipoprotein (HDL), low-density lipoprotein (LDL), height and body weight were measured at both baseline and follow-up.
LimitationsThe sample size is only one, because the author fail to find more volunteer to participate in this study.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>